<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Projects on Yolanda&#39;s Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Projects on Yolanda&#39;s Personal Website</description>
    <image>
      <title>Yolanda&#39;s Personal Website</title>
      <url>https://yolandapan02.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://yolandapan02.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.143.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Borders: Pechoin&#39;s Global Expansion Strategy from Malaysia to Southeast Asia</title>
      <link>https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/ow_case_competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/ow_case_competition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;
    .project-intro {
        background-color: #f8f9fa;
        padding: 25px;
        border-left: 4px solid #4a4a4a;
        margin-bottom: 20px;
        line-height: 1.8;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;project-intro&#34;&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;This project represents comprehensive strategic analysis for Pechoin, a leading Chinese skincare brand. As team leader for this Oliver Wyman Impact Competition entry, I developed a data-driven expansion strategy identifying Malaysia as the optimal entry point into Southeast Asian markets based on consumer preferences, competitive landscape, and cultural alignment.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The project addressed critical business challenges through quantitative analysis of beauty industry trends and consumer data. Our strategy integrated a three-pillar brand positioning, tailored product matrix, omni-channel approach, and comprehensive supply chain solution. Financial modeling projected a pathway to $20 million in annual profits by 2030, with planned expansion to Singapore and Indonesia in years 3-5, demonstrating how systematic market analysis creates actionable strategies in competitive markets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, Sentiment Analysis, and United HealthCare CEO Shooting</title>
      <link>https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/proj_uhc_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yolandapan02.github.io/projects/proj_uhc_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Question:&lt;/strong&gt; How has public opinion related to health insurance changed in the wake of the UnitedHealthcare CEO shooting?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RQ Formulated as an ML Task:&lt;/strong&gt; In order to see how public opinion related to health insurance has changed in the wake of the UnitedHealthcare CEO shooting, we will conduct a machine learning classification task to predict whether Reddit posts have positive, negative, or neutral sentiments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Collection:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;arctic_shift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raw data downloads in .jsonl format&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document contains dictionaries of data
related to each comment, including
metadata, date posted (in unicode
format), username of poster, and text
from the post&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our dataset: a dictionary mapping each
unicode date (key) to its corresponding
text content (value)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Labeling:&lt;/strong&gt;
Using a stratified sampling method, we selected a random subset of 1,000 comments for hand-labeling, which we then used to train our model.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
